[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "did you now have sufficient time to discuss with your attorneys whether or not you wanted to testify in this case?", "question_tokens": ["did", "you", "now", "have", "sufficient", "time", "to", "discuss", "with", "your", "attorneys", "whether", "or", "not", "you", "wanted", "to", "testify", "in", "this", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "ma'am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "And I don't need to know what was said, but after those discussions, have you made a decision?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "do", "n't", "need", "to", "know", "what", "was", "said", ",", "but", "after", "those", "discussions", ",", "have", "you", "made", "a", "decision", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "ma'am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "And what is your decision, sir?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "your", "decision", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "After consulting with counsel, not to testify, Your Honor.", "answer_tokens": ["After", "consulting", "with", "counsel", ",", "not", "to", "testify", ",", "Your", "Honor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "If this person, this mannequin, were carrying a firearm on their waist, where would the gun be right now in relation to me?", "question_tokens": ["If", "this", "person", ",", "this", "mannequin", ",", "were", "carrying", "a", "firearm", "on", "their", "waist", ",", "where", "would", "the", "gun", "be", "right", "now", "in", "relation", "to", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Would be at your left inner thigh.", "answer_tokens": ["Would", "be", "at", "your", "left", "inner", "thigh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Right here, right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "here", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Yes, if he was right-handed it would be at your left inner thigh.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "if", "he", "was", "right-handed", "it", "would", "be", "at", "your", "left", "inner", "thigh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Right, underneath my leg?", "question_tokens": ["Right", ",", "underneath", "my", "leg", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes, inside your leg.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "inside", "your", "leg", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Were you aware of that?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "aware", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "No, I haven't heard that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "heard", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Where would the gun be now?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "would", "the", "gun", "be", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Now the gun would be behind your left leg.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "the", "gun", "would", "be", "behind", "your", "left", "leg", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Have you made a decision, sir, as to whether or not you want to testify in your case?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "made", "a", "decision", ",", "sir", ",", "as", "to", "whether", "or", "not", "you", "want", "to", "testify", "in", "your", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "TO", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Your honor, I object to that question.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "honor", ",", "I", "object", "to", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", ":"], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Do you have made a decision as to whether or not you want to testify in your case?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "made", "a", "decision", "as", "to", "whether", "or", "not", "you", "want", "to", "testify", "in", "your", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I object to that question, I think that's --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "object", "to", "that", "question", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 81, "question": "If your attorneys have finished with two witnesses before the end of the day, do you think that you would then know whether or not you want to testify?", "question_tokens": ["If", "your", "attorneys", "have", "finished", "with", "two", "witnesses", "before", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "you", "would", "then", "know", "whether", "or", "not", "you", "want", "to", "testify", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I'll -- on Mr. Zimmerman's behalf this --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "--", "on", "Mr.", "Zimmerman", "'s", "behalf", "this", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "And quickly, Martin, what do we expect tomorrow and more importantly, can we expect the jury to go out as soon as Friday, perhaps?", "question_tokens": ["And", "quickly", ",", "Martin", ",", "what", "do", "we", "expect", "tomorrow", "and", "more", "importantly", ",", "can", "we", "expect", "the", "jury", "to", "go", "out", "as", "soon", "as", "Friday", ",", "perhaps", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Yes, we can.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"], "PERSON": ["Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Do you feel confident you've proven a case collectively that Trayvon Martin was murdered?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "confident", "you", "'ve", "proven", "a", "case", "collectively", "that", "Trayvon", "Martin", "was", "murdered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Piers, you're right and I'm glad to be free from being sequestered so I can now talk about the case and I've been catching up throughout the day looking at different clips after it was determined they -- the defense was not going to call me to testify.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "you", "'re", "right", "and", "I", "'m", "glad", "to", "be", "free", "from", "being", "sequestered", "so", "I", "can", "now", "talk", "about", "the", "case", "and", "I", "'ve", "been", "catching", "up", "throughout", "the", "day", "looking", "at", "different", "clips", "after", "it", "was", "determined", "they", "--", "the", "defense", "was", "not", "going", "to", "call", "me", "to", "testify", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Crump"]}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "And so we can never get beyond Trayvon Martin just walking home and a strange man chasing him, doesn't Trayvon Martin have the right to self-defense?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", "we", "can", "never", "get", "beyond", "Trayvon", "Martin", "just", "walking", "home", "and", "a", "strange", "man", "chasing", "him", ",", "does", "n't", "Trayvon", "Martin", "have", "the", "right", "to", "self-defense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "But here's the problem, Ben Crump, is that many people will have absolute sympathy with what you're saying, but at the same time you say chase the evidence.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "here", "'s", "the", "problem", ",", "Ben", "Crump", ",", "is", "that", "many", "people", "will", "have", "absolute", "sympathy", "with", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", ",", "but", "at", "the", "same", "time", "you", "say", "chase", "the", "evidence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Regardless of that, you are now left with the jury that believed Trayvon was on top and they are more likely, are they not, to assume that the voice crying out for help is the person underneath?", "question_tokens": ["Regardless", "of", "that", ",", "you", "are", "now", "left", "with", "the", "jury", "that", "believed", "Trayvon", "was", "on", "top", "and", "they", "are", "more", "likely", ",", "are", "they", "not", ",", "to", "assume", "that", "the", "voice", "crying", "out", "for", "help", "is", "the", "person", "underneath", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Piers, it has always been our contention that there was some struggle and if Trayvon defended himself against a strange man who confronted him, he had every right to do so.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "it", "has", "always", "been", "our", "contention", "that", "there", "was", "some", "struggle", "and", "if", "Trayvon", "defended", "himself", "against", "a", "strange", "man", "who", "confronted", "him", ",", "he", "had", "every", "right", "to", "do", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Could you see a situation where George Zimmerman is convicted of one of those lesser charges, and would that be satisfactory if you couldn't get a murder charge against him?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "see", "a", "situation", "where", "George", "Zimmerman", "is", "convicted", "of", "one", "of", "those", "lesser", "charges", ",", "and", "would", "that", "be", "satisfactory", "if", "you", "could", "n't", "get", "a", "murder", "charge", "against", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "MD", "IN", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Well, what's satisfactory is what the jury decides in this case.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "'s", "satisfactory", "is", "what", "the", "jury", "decides", "in", "this", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What are you detecting if you can from the mood of this jury right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "detecting", "if", "you", "can", "from", "the", "mood", "of", "this", "jury", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well, today was fascinating, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "today", "was", "fascinating", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "And what did you tell them?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "you", "tell", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "I told them absolutely, it's my son, George.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "told", "them", "absolutely", ",", "it", "'s", "my", "son", ",", "George", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Is that an opinion that you still have through today?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "an", "opinion", "that", "you", "still", "have", "through", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Certainly.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "I mean, Judge Hatchett, you know, that is a view many people have and also they say to me, look, what about Trayvon Martin's right to defend himself?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Judge", "Hatchett", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "is", "a", "view", "many", "people", "have", "and", "also", "they", "say", "to", "me", ",", "look", ",", "what", "about", "Trayvon", "Martin", "'s", "right", "to", "defend", "himself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judge Hatchett", "Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Wasn't he engaged in a form of self-defense himself and where does his right to do that supersede George Zimmerman who's got a gun?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "he", "engaged", "in", "a", "form", "of", "self-defense", "himself", "and", "where", "does", "his", "right", "to", "do", "that", "supersede", "George", "Zimmerman", "who", "'s", "got", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "POS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Right, I tell you, I -- Tom has just articulated so perfectly.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "I", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "--", "Tom", "has", "just", "articulated", "so", "perfectly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Why -- why are you so aggressively ante that statement?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "--", "why", "are", "you", "so", "aggressively", "ante", "that", "statement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "I'll tell you why.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "What else is he doing to Trayvon Martin but profiling him as a bad guy that needs to be dealt with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "is", "he", "doing", "to", "Trayvon", "Martin", "but", "profiling", "him", "as", "a", "bad", "guy", "that", "needs", "to", "be", "dealt", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "OBBINS: Yes, I think that's absolutely right.", "answer_tokens": ["OBBINS", ":", "Yes", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "absolutely", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Based upon your training experience and knowing what you knew about the facts surrounding the event that night, particularly at the moment of the gunshot, did Mr. Zimmerman have any other options?", "question_tokens": ["Based", "upon", "your", "training", "experience", "and", "knowing", "what", "you", "knew", "about", "the", "facts", "surrounding", "the", "event", "that", "night", ",", "particularly", "at", "the", "moment", "of", "the", "gunshot", ",", "did", "Mr.", "Zimmerman", "have", "any", "other", "options", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "OOT: Based on my knowledge and understanding of him, the environment, the situation, the totality of everything, I don't believe he did.", "answer_tokens": ["OOT", ":", "Based", "on", "my", "knowledge", "and", "understanding", "of", "him", ",", "the", "environment", ",", "the", "situation", ",", "the", "totality", "of", "everything", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What do you think the rational is behind what many view as a very surprising decision by him to say I had nothing to do with this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "rational", "is", "behind", "what", "many", "view", "as", "a", "very", "surprising", "decision", "by", "him", "to", "say", "I", "had", "nothing", "to", "do", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I think this is a formal aspect of a criminal case.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "this", "is", "a", "formal", "aspect", "of", "a", "criminal", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "LOCATION": ["Chicago"], "PERSON": ["David Webb", "Bill O'Reilly", "Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Let me ask you, David Webb, I mean, people like Bill O'Reilly have made the point, look, you know, there are -- in Chicago over the long holiday weekend, nearly 70 people were shot, many of them young black youths shooting each other, and it barely resonates on the national stage, yet here we are gripped by the Zimmerman- Trayvon Martin case.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "David", "Webb", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "people", "like", "Bill", "O'Reilly", "have", "made", "the", "point", ",", "look", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "are", "--", "in", "Chicago", "over", "the", "long", "holiday", "weekend", ",", "nearly", "70", "people", "were", "shot", ",", "many", "of", "them", "young", "black", "youths", "shooting", "each", "other", ",", "and", "it", "barely", "resonates", "on", "the", "national", "stage", ",", "yet", "here", "we", "are", "gripped", "by", "the", "Zimmerman-", "Trayvon", "Martin", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trevor Dooley"], "LOCATION": ["Florida", "Florida"]}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Why is the balance so skewed toward this case and not to 70 shot in Chicago?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "the", "balance", "so", "skewed", "toward", "this", "case", "and", "not", "to", "70", "shot", "in", "Chicago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Or to Trevor Dooley who by the way is a black man who used Florida's Stand Your Ground law to defend himself when he shot a white man and this case is also down in Florida.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "to", "Trevor", "Dooley", "who", "by", "the", "way", "is", "a", "black", "man", "who", "used", "Florida", "'s", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "law", "to", "defend", "himself", "when", "he", "shot", "a", "white", "man", "and", "this", "case", "is", "also", "down", "in", "Florida", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "What matters is did George Zimmerman think I'm going to die?", "question_tokens": ["What", "matters", "is", "did", "George", "Zimmerman", "think", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "die", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "I mean, we don't actually know, do we?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "actually", "know", ",", "do", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Well, here are the inconsistencies with that story.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "are", "the", "inconsistencies", "with", "that", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Where has anybody directly contradicted evidentially something material and important that George Zimmerman has said?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "has", "anybody", "directly", "contradicted", "evidentially", "something", "material", "and", "important", "that", "George", "Zimmerman", "has", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Well, this is -- and here --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "--", "and", "here", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Does that make sense?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "make", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "That's --", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Final question, what do you think they're going to do?", "question_tokens": ["Final", "question", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "David?", "question_tokens": ["David", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I think the prosecution has not made the case for second- degree murder.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "prosecution", "has", "not", "made", "the", "case", "for", "second-", "degree", "murder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "How about manslaughter or aggravated assault?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "manslaughter", "or", "aggravated", "assault", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "JJR", "CC", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Possibly down and depends on the instructions but they have not made the case beyond a reasonable doubt.", "answer_tokens": ["Possibly", "down", "and", "depends", "on", "the", "instructions", "but", "they", "have", "not", "made", "the", "case", "beyond", "a", "reasonable", "doubt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "What do you make of this trial?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "trial", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Well, you know, I look at it first as a lawyer and the legal issues I think have been articulated pretty well on many of your programs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "look", "at", "it", "first", "as", "a", "lawyer", "and", "the", "legal", "issues", "I", "think", "have", "been", "articulated", "pretty", "well", "on", "many", "of", "your", "programs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "I mean, here's the question I think that, you know, someone just raised to me during the break there, which is that if George Zimmerman hadn't had the gun on him, would he have felt empowered or courageous enough to have got out of his vehicle and to have started walking in the direction of this tall young black teenager?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "here", "'s", "the", "question", "I", "think", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "someone", "just", "raised", "to", "me", "during", "the", "break", "there", ",", "which", "is", "that", "if", "George", "Zimmerman", "had", "n't", "had", "the", "gun", "on", "him", ",", "would", "he", "have", "felt", "empowered", "or", "courageous", "enough", "to", "have", "got", "out", "of", "his", "vehicle", "and", "to", "have", "started", "walking", "in", "the", "direction", "of", "this", "tall", "young", "black", "teenager", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "I mean, the thing is a total farce, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "the", "thing", "is", "a", "total", "farce", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Well, it doesn't make a lot of sense to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "make", "a", "lot", "of", "sense", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "How important do you think will be the fact that the jury is entirely female and five of them are mothers?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "do", "you", "think", "will", "be", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "jury", "is", "entirely", "female", "and", "five", "of", "them", "are", "mothers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "UROW: You know, the classic learning on this, I think that the prosecution is hoping that they see Trayvon as their child, and they may.", "answer_tokens": ["UROW", ":", "You", "know", ",", "the", "classic", "learning", "on", "this", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "prosecution", "is", "hoping", "that", "they", "see", "Trayvon", "as", "their", "child", ",", "and", "they", "may", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130710pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "If we -- if we got to the last page of a book you'd written about this case, Scott, would you have guilty or not guilty?", "question_tokens": ["If", "we", "--", "if", "we", "got", "to", "the", "last", "page", "of", "a", "book", "you", "'d", "written", "about", "this", "case", ",", "Scott", ",", "would", "you", "have", "guilty", "or", "not", "guilty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I don't think Mr. Zimmerman is going to be convicted.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "Mr.", "Zimmerman", "is", "going", "to", "be", "convicted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scott"]}}]